#### Contact

fahadsheikhmuhammad10@gmail .com

www.linkedin.com/in/fahad-sheikh-muhammad-17305821a (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Project Management Quality Control Business Operations

### Certifications

Introduction to Data Engineering
Databases and SQL for Data
Science with Python

# Fahad Sheikh Muhammad

Data Analyst | Data Engineer | Operations Manager | Business Enthusiast | Brand Manager

Karāchi

## Summary

Experienced Operations Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the apparel and fashion industry. Skilled in Business Operations, Quality Control, Python (Programming Language), SQL, and Microsoft Excel. Strong business development professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer science from Bahria University.

## Experience

Reverb Universe Apparel Web Developer and Analyst November 2019 - Present (2 years 2 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

International Watch Company Order Database Manager April 2020 - March 2021 (1 year) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

National Investment Trust Limited Intern Information Technology Department July 2019 - September 2019 (3 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

### Education

Bahria University

Bachelor's degree, Computer science · (September 2017 - August 2021)

Delhi Government College

Intermediate, Pre-Engineering · (August 2015 - August 2017)

BVS Parsi High School

SSC, Computer Science · (August 2010 - July 2015)